Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING
THE FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION
Let go of me, let go!
Are you out of your breath...
... because you are fighting
for freedom, Osman?
I will kill you with my
own hands, Dündar Bey!
What is it, are you going after
what is mine, Osman Bey?
No.
Did you really think you could
take Genghis Khan's legacy from me?
Come on, you idiots, come on, hurry!
If something happens to this woman,
even I can't save you from Balgay's wrath.
As you say, Cerkutay.
Take the woman to
Balgay without hurting her.
You follow me, we have some
unfinished business.
Osman Bey.
Dündar Bey!
You became allies with the
Mongols for my father's place!
You made your son, Batur
partner for your treason!
Enough, Osman.
Enough.
You did all this because of your
irresponsible, reckless, childish acts.
You will pay for your doings, not Kayıs!
You will burn in the fire of
rebellion that you started.
I will make my father's tent your grave!
Wolves are with the wolves.
Jackals are with the jackals.
Jackals' reign ends...
... when wolves stand up!
I will kill you with my
own hands, Dündar Bey!
This Tent is ruled
with Genghis Khan's laws...
... not with Oguz's traditions.
You will not live until you see the
consequences of your treason, Osman Bey.
- Balgay-
- Later, Kongar.
Die, Osman!
Freedom or death!
Die!
Die, Osman!
I came here to take what is Geyhatu's.
I was able to take Genghis
Khan's laws from Osman's hands.
The laws are my gift to Geyhatu.
And the blessed dagger.
Geyhatu...
... won't leave this victory
of yours without a prize.
Don't you worry, Balgay.
Is this Osman?
Yes.
My Allah, don't let me perish
in the hands of the enemy.
Let me die while fighting.
Osman Bey is a prisoner of Geyhatu.
We will take him to Konya.
Soldiers.
Take Osman Bey to the cart.
Cauterize his wounds.
No one will get near him.
Balgay.
Come with me to the tent.
I have news from Geyhatu.
You should come too.
My Osman!
Stop!
You are the banner lord now.
Commander Balgay decided it was suitable.
Nothing is suitable if
Geyhatu is not informed.
But, if Balgay decided it...
... he must know something.
I will have my eyes on you...
... and my ears in your Tent...
Dündar.
Now go.
I want to take Genghis
Khan's laws to Konya personally.
Don't worry, Geyhatu will know you are the
one who found and give the laws to him.
What is it with taking Osman to Konya?
Geyhatu wants to interrogate
Osman to find out how he got the laws.
He is not your prisoner anymore.
Are you afraid of something, Balgay?
Osman, my Osman, Osman!
Ya Allah!
Stay away! We don't want trouble!
Osman will be taken away!
I am talking to you, Balgay.
Is there something that concerns you?
I don't have any
concerns, Commander Köni.
Geyhatu should know that I am
ready to die for him, that's enough.
What if Osman tell Geyhatu everything?
Kill Köni and his soldiers.
Take Osman and the laws to me.
As you command, Commander Balgay.
Show yourself!
My Allah...
... give me strength.
Brothers, don't you despair
brothers and sisters!
Stand strong, Kayı Tent!
We will stand strong!
We will stand strong, Kayı Tent!
No one can bend our knees!
Even if they make all
the world a prison...
... we will never give up our cause!
Freedom or death!
Allahu Akbar!
[Allah is the greatest!]
Dündar Bey.
Wait for my word.
Because our enemies grow in number.
Don't you ever forget that I am the one
who gave you the rank of banner lord.
My loyalty to you knows no limits, Balgay.
Show yourself!
Where are you?
Show yourself, where are you?
Batur.
Batur!
I thought you were a man!
But there is a snake in your heart!
Shame on you, Batur.
You make Kayı Tent
bleed with your treason!
Bamsı Bey, Abdurrahman Gazi...
Osman saw you as a brother, he risked
his life for you, all my efforts for you-
Stop, woman, do you think my son is alone,
that you judge without listening?
I did all this.
Me.
Your Bey did it.
Your banner lord, that
you dislike, disobey!
Are you hearing your
own words, Dündar Bey?
I am, I am.
How do you think Köni
came here, Bamsı Bey?
Who planned this game, who do you
think repelled all those jackals around?
I did it.
I personally sent word to the Mongolian
governor in Konya, made the two dogs fight!
Now...
... that dog, Balgay will get angry,
and they will enter a battle.
I got nothing else to do
to keep my Tent safe.
If something happens to Osman, if they kill
him in Konya, what will you do, Dündar Bey?
Then what will you do, Dündar Bey?
If something happens to Osman, if they kill
him in Konya, what will you do, Dündar Bey?
Then what will you do, Dündar Bey?
They promised.
They swore!
They won't hurt Osman.
They'll just interrogate him.
We got it. You're not a traitor.
But you're naive, Dündar. Naive!
How can you trust the Mongols?
Not just Batur. Shame on both of you!
Shame on you too!
If something happens to Osman,
then I'll become an eagle and...
... dismember you with my own claws.
Know that, Dündar Bey!
Listen to me carefully, Selcan Hatun.
You're not looking at the old Dündar.
After your smallest mistake,
I'll rip your claws off and...
... break your wings. Know that.
Giddy up!
Kayı Tent loves you very much.
They love fighting the cruel more.
You look like you're sure
that you'll return.
Who said Geyhatu will release you?
You came here without knowing
who we are, Köni.
We have hejira within our migration,
reclusion within our sorrow...
... testimony within our revenge.
- Bamsı Bey!
- Sons!
Where is that dog Balgay?
Balgay didn't take Osman.
It's Geyhatu's helper Köni.
So Geyhatu is aware of Genghis' Laws.
So we've found a new enemy.
It doesn't matter if Genghis
comes out of his grave.
We'll not let those infidels decide
Osman's fate! Come on valiants!
My Osman!
The prisoner is running away!
Get him!
Köni!
Kongar!
Kill them all!
Where is Osman?
- Where is the Genghis Khans' law?
- Geyhatu will make you pay for this!
There is no one left to inform
Geyhatu, Köni.
You'll die too!
You're wrong! Osman will be your end!
So you let Osman take the laws too, fool!
Find Osman! If you can't,
I'll rip your hearts out!
These are Balgay's men. They killed
Köni too.
Osman Bey is nowhere to be seen either.
Bamsı Bey. Isn't this dagger yours?
It's mine. Where did you find this?
There's a dead body by the cart. I took
it from his neck.
Good. So Osman managed to run away before
Balgay's dogs arrived.
Good. Good. Come on, lions. We need to
find Osman before those infidels!
We won't let dogs get our lion, my Bey.
- We won't. Come on, valiants.
- Let's go.
Until I get to smell your silky hair,
wrap this scarf on your head.
Every time I pray to Allah almighty,
your name is in my prayers.
I pray that Allah resigns us to
each other for eternity.
Osman!
Forgive me.
I left you alone in your hard days.
Alaca!
Don't be scared. You're safe.
- Who are you?
- Don't worry about who I am.
Your wound needs to be cleaned and seared.
You need to hold on.
Bala!
Bala, where are you?
Where are you, Bala?
Where are you?
Alaca! Where is my Bala?
Where is my Bala?
Where is she?
There are two guests at
my traceless house today.
Who are you?
I'm l--
I'm looking for someone.
My horse is by the stable.
Osman!
- Bala!
- Osman!
What did they do to you? Tell me, my dear.
What did they do to you?
Bala! Tell me! Who did this to you?
Who did this to you?
I'm okay. Who did this?
Tell me! Tell me and
I'll go rip his heart out!
Cerkutay!
They crossed my path.
Son! Allow me for a second.
Son! It should not cool down.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
( in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate.)
Will she live?
Tell me. Will she live?
I don't know. I did my best.
The rest is for Allah to decide.
You're not okay.
Go lay there.
Those cruel dogs!
I'll give you the worst of deaths!
Mother!
She is my dearest.
Don't let her fade away.
Save her. Save her.
My Allah, help this poor servant of yours.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
( in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate.)
"May the peace and mercy of
Allah be with you."
My Allah, keeper of everything...
You command everything.
You're capable. You possess real
power and potency.
Ya Rab! Your people are in misery!
Not only the cruel and intruders...
... unrest and disunion also
captured them.
We forgot about the greatest thing
that held us together.
Muslim Brotherhood.
We lost trust for each other.
We gave in to our desires.
My Rab, who knows everything!
Clean our hearts' dirt with
the light of Islam.
Enlighten us. Forgive us.
Allow us to be strong
against infidelity...
... the cruel and the devil's tricks.
My Allah! Make us go through
Sirat al-Mustaqim.
Allow us to be like those who always
follow the right path...
... and die for this cause.
Ya Rab!
Scatter our darkness into the courtesy of
the name El Fettah...
... allow us to destroy infidelity.
To us, to those Muslims
waiting for hope...
... to the poor waiting for
the good news...
... allow us to rise anew.
Greetings, friend.
Aleyküm Selam. What is it, Bamsı Bey?
Friend, Geyhatu's men came from Konya
to take Osman.
Osman ran away from them,
but now we can't find him.
As if the ground swallowed him.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
( in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate.)
Bala Hatun is also lost.
We're looking for her everywhere.
Do you think something happened to them?
What if the Mongols got them again?
The things which saved Yusuf
from the well...
... Ibrahim from fire...
... İsmail from knives...
... is both faith and effort, Bamsı Bey.
There's no time to stop.
We shall go look for them.
We take the measures
and let Allah decide it's fate.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, friend. Here.
Come on, lions! Let's go!
Where are you, Bala? Where are you?
- What happened here, Gonca Hatun?
- They had a battle, Pehlivan Dervish!
Blood everywhere!
I found the fardel over there!
There is someone's things inside.
But nothing from Bala Hatun.
Bala! Bala!
These ornaments! They are Bala's.
Friends! Keep looking. I'll go to the
Kayı Tent. I need to find Selcan Hatun.
- Okay.
- Good bye.
You too.
Men of my Tent!
Çetin Alp will take you somewhere safe.
And we'll go up to the mountains and
light the fire of rebellion.
We won't rest until we kick those
Mongols who invade our lands!
We're not looking for rest, Samsa Bey!
Don't look at our ages.
We have breaths powerful enough
to disperse nine armies in one shout.
You gave up on your chance
of testimony, Sazak Bey.
Now it's time for us to fight.
May Allah not let you die in your sleep.
Amin.
First Allah, then you will take care of
the men, women and children, Çetin Alp.
- Thank you, my Bey!
- Thank you.
My men, standing still like mountains!
You have my blessings. I expect the same.
You have our blessings, my Bey!
- Long live Samsa Bey!
You shall fall victim to
the dark spirits' wrath, Cergutay!
How can you let a wounded
Hatun run away from you?
How can you be such a fool?
You'll pay for this!
- Did you take care of it?
- Commander Balgay...
I killed Köni and his soldiers. They are
no longer a threat for us.
Good. What about Osman?
Genghis Khan's laws?
When I arrived, Osman had already left.
Commander Balgay. Osman ran away
with Genghis Khans' laws.
I sent my soldiers after him.
Osman is wounded and alone. We'll
eventually find him, Commander Balgay.
You'll tell Geyhatu that
his soldiers killed Osman.
Send a messenger to Konya.
Tell what happened as I said.
As you wish, Balgay.
For the wrath of the spirits...
Erlik Khan's curse to Osman...
Call Zöhre here.
I want her to come here tomorrow,
secretly.
Dündar shouldn't know this.
She'll tell me where Geyhatu heard that
I had Genghis Khans' laws.
Come on! What are you waiting for?
Osman!
So Samsa climbed the mountains
and rebelled against Balgay?
He took his Tent's men, women, and
children to somewhere safe.
And tomorrow he will go to
Şahin Hill with his Alps.
Brave enough to fight Balgay with
a handful of Alps...
... dumb enough to think that he'll
win this battle.
Miserable enough to deserve to die
with Balgay's grudge.
How did Balgay know that Samsa will
go the Şahin Hill tomorrow?
This has one answer, Master Yannis.
Balgay must have bought one
of Samsa's Beys.
We have to put a spy among
Balgay's commanders.
I'll do what is necessary, Sofia.
- Who do you have in mind?
- Everyone in this world has a price.
Or a weakness.
Master Yannis.
Osman escaped from Geyhatu's
soldiers, Salvador.
I'm not surprised.
Osman is like oil.
No one can hold him.
To deal with Osman, one needs to separate
his head from his body.
This is the right time for you to
take us where...
... he and his Alps are hiding, Salvador.
Make sure Osman is there when
we ambush them.
I'll be commanding the soldiers.
And I'll be with you, Princess Sofia.
My valiant warrior Salvador.
Now go, start preparing.
You will capture Osman, Sofia. You will
take Genghis Khan's laws.
Balgay shouldn't come to the ambush.
Do you understand?
Don't worry, Master Yannis.
- Selcan Hatun!
- I hope nothing's wrong!
- Bala! She's lost.
- What do you mean she's lost.
She said she'll be meeting with you.
I said I should come too.
I don't want you to go alone, I said.
She didn't listen. She went.
She didn't return.
Dervishes are looking for here everwhere.
No one saw or heard of her.
Look what happened! Are there no traces?
We found a fardel. But the things inside
are not Bala's.
They are men's clothes.
Zöhre!
There were bloodstains where
we found the fardel.
There was a fight for sure.
We found Bala's silver ornaments.
Selcan Hatun! I'm begging you,
we should tell Osman Bey.
No one else can find Bala.
Osman! My Osman!
Osman...
Bala...
She can't hear you.
She's in another world right now.
Drink.
You need strength.
It's not enough for you. Wait.
I had some jerky.
She'll live, right, mother?
She'll be okay, right?
Blind love...
You escaped death, and you're still
thinking about her.
She'll live, hopefully.
If she goes, half of my heart goes too.
Then even if I set the whole world
on fire...
... my anger for those who did this to her
will not go away.
Your heart is strong like your arms.
Such a heart is needed for such a love.
Tell me. Where are you from, Osman Bey?
From the Kayıs. How do you know my name?
She kept saying Osman.
It's obvious that it's you.
Who are you? Where are you from?
They call me Elif Hatun.
If you have no friends or relatives,
no one calls your name.
Why are you living in this cave?
Isn't it hard being alone?
I don't like people. I don't like to
expect things from servants of Allah.
I ran away to here years ago.
There is nothing but peace.
Not just one, but two people.
Wounded too. We broke your
peace, mother Elif.
May Allah bless you. You healed us.
You'll be fine.
This cave will be mine again.
A man whose heavy injuries heal fast,
is a real valiant.
How magnificent! You're very strong.
I lost a lot of blood. I need strength.
I need to stand upright, mother!
There are a lot of enemies.
They are also harsh.
If she's fine, it's alright.
I want her to be in my sight.
A battle doesn't scare me.
Still nothing from Osman, huh?
No, father. But don't worry.
The Alps are always on the watch.
He can't come close to the Tent.
Batur! You still need to be careful!
We're talking about Osman. You can't know
what he will do.
Uncle!
What do you think you're doing, Uncle?
How can you let them take Osman?
These...
These are my fathers Beyhood symbols.
How can you bring those
to your tent, uncle?
What are you trying to do, uncle?
These belong to the Kayı's
Bey, not Ertuğrul Gazi.
So? How can you take
them before my father dies?
You don't know the situation
since you were in Nikea.
Now, I'm the Bey. Know your limits.
Laws decide the limits, Dündar Bey!
Is Kayı's throne something they
sell at the bazaar? How can you do this?
Bey orders, Head Alp does.
Watch your words, Gündüz Bey.
I don't need younglings
to teach me the law!
Don't make me a nephew killer!
Get out of my tent!
Get out!
Gündüz! Calm down, Gündüz.
Get a hold of yourself.
Ayşe! I will not see you
in this tent ever again!
From now on, we're done with this place!
War shall wait.
You should get better.
Both the war and enemy don't wait.
Those dogs bide their time to attack.
My weapon shall be ready.
I will not stop.
Bala.
Thank my Allah.
Look at me.
Look at me so I celebrate it.
You shall bring wood.
She needs to be warm.
I would burn the mountain for her.
She shall be warm.
You are going to get better, Bala.
It's all going to be fine. Mother Elif
is here. I'll be right back.
Get yourself up a little bit.
Thank Allah you opened your eyes.
Drink. It's healthy.
You should drink something.
Thank you, mother.
The pain has spread to my legs.
They are getting numb.
It's okay, isn't it?
Your legs are going to be fine,
in sha Allah.
What about the rest?
Tell me.
I don't want it anymore.
You are not telling me.
Tell me what you are hiding, mother.
I did my best.
And Allah allowed you and didn't take
your life.
However, your wound is in a bad place.
Some wounds leave a trace on the body,
while some in the soul.
Your wound is in your soul.
Look, my daughter, if you question why
in this universe, you will get nowhere.
The doors will open to those who consent.
What do you mean, mother?
Say it directly.
Obviously, warrior girl, you can't
have children.
How?
Destiny.
I don't know if your situation recover.
Allah is the owner of miracles.
Mother Sahre became a mother in
ninety years old.
Maybe a Hatun whose uterus doesn't work
have children.
Only Allah knows.
What are you talking about, mother?
What are you talking about?
I will flare the fire up.
I will warm here.
Take me to dark souls, shaman drum.
Dark souls shall hear my oath.
They shall take my soul to the Erlik
Han's dark palace, with dark mud and iron.
My oath is for Erlik Han.
Erlik Han, this is Balgay's oath for you.
I will irrigate your palace with that
Turk, Osman.
I will sacrifice his soul for you, I will
give his body to ravens.
Listen to Balgay's voice that reaches to
you via the shaman drum.
You shall show me Osman.
If I don't keep my promise...
May blue sky and dark wind take my
soul.
My soul shall...
suffer in pain forever.
Erlik Han...
Give me Osman!
Mother Elif is strange.
Not grim, and not absolutely harsh.
However, she is useful.
Moreover, she will make you poultice.
Smile please.
It's all gone.
We have a lot of trouble and enemy.
Our only aim is to hold onto each other.
Once we get rid of those troubles
I will want you in marriage from
my Sheik.
We will have a great garden.
We will have children.
We will accrue so that we gain power.
Once you get out of this situation...
the rest is destiny, Osman.
It is obvious that you have difficult ways
in front of you.
However, you will be stronger with
your children.
Everyone will hear about Osman's
sons.
They will know about you. You will
forget the pain.
Your journey will be magnificent like you.
- May Allah give you the victory.
- What is that about, Bala Hatun?
You speak like you are leaving me.
I pray for our journey to be together.
Why do you speak like that?
I'd die for you, Osman.
Of course I will stand by you.
Destiny.
You have pain. I know that
you'll smile when you get better.
Everything is going to be fine.
These difficult days will be gone.
May my Allah give us...
daughters and sons.
If I am their father, I want you to be
their mother as well.
Inshallah this will happen.
Inshallah.
Amin.
Don't think about me, Osman.
They say, "Men plan god laughs."
Allah is great.
May he give you what you want.
Eeh, I understand, I understand.
You will be delicate when you are sick.
It's okay.
It's no problem when it's about you.
Mother Elif.
Bala Hatun is entrusted to you.
- Take her to her father.
- Who is her father? Where can I find?
Bala Hatun will show you the way.
He is Sheik Edebalı.
Sheik Edebalı?
Allah will give me his beloved creature's
praying.
My Sheik, you have been up for all night.
You are tired.
They will surely find both Osman and
Bala Hatun. You should have some rest.
- Our Allah is greater than our trouble.
- Of course.
Of course he is the one.
Right, Gonca daughter?
Like you say, my Sheik.
My Allah is greater than our trouble.
But I am desperate.
I think of Bala.
We always think of Bala.
However, if there is an examination,
there is always a help
You shall relax.
- Bala!
- Bala, my daughter!
Thank Allah, come here. Come.
- She is wounded, be careful.
- Easy, easy.
Easy, come daughter, easy.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
(In the name of God, the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful)
Thank Allah.
Thank my Allah.
May Allah bless you, Hatun.
You united me and my daughter.
May Allah give you what you want.
I don't want anything else than a prayer
of a saint like you, Sheik Edeblaı.
I brought Osman Bey's greetings as well.
He is valiant.
Yes he is.
You shall sit, Hatun.
Catch your breath.
Tell me, what is Osman Bey's situation?
Get up.
I told you where to find Osman and Edebalı.
I told the truth.
I want you more.
I kept my promise.
My son is under your guard, from now on.
-What do you want more?
- Shut up, woman, shut up!
Who told Geyhatu that I have Cengiz
Han's laws?
I don't know.
Cerkutay, bring this woman's son Batur
at once.
I will make a crib out of his skin and
swing his mother in it.
No, stop. No, I said stop.
Stop, stop, stop.
Talk.
Talk!
Who!
Who told Geyhatu that I have Cengiz Han's
laws?
Who?
I am asking you for the last time.
Either you tell me that dog's name...
or I will give Batu's head to you and
bury you alive.
Who?
Those are my father's Beyship signs.
How can you take them to your tent, uncle?
Those do not belong to Ertuğrul Bey,
but to the Kayı Bey.
How can you take them while
my father is still alive?
You don't know about things because
you were away.
Gündüz.
Osman's brother Gündüz?
Yes, he is.
Two days ago, he left the tribe.
We thought he went to Nike.
But he went to Konya.
He brought Commander Köni and his
Nökers (soldiers) to the tribe.
I told you.
What do you want more?
What about Osman.
I don't know about Osman.
Who is close to Osman in the tribe?
Samsa Bey and Bamsı Bey are close to Osman.
Osman is with them.
How can they be?
Osman and Samsa are enemies.
They know how to unite against
the enemy.
If you find Samsa...
you will find Osman, Balgay.
I know where Samsa is.
Cerkutay, tell Kongor to kill them all
with his best Nökers (soldiers).
I want Osman and Cengiz Han's laws alive.
Bring them to Kulucahisar Castle.
Why are you still here, woman?
Get out!
Blood.
People are coming.
Are there any news?
Unfortunately, no.
My sons!
Just as Osman didn't surrender to those
savages in Konya...
...we won't surrender to laziness.
We must do everything to save our Osman.
My Osman!
My Bey!
My Rab has answered to our prayers.
My Osman!
Oh, thank you my Rab!
Praise Allah!
My Bey!
How mighty!
Thanks to our Allah.
My Bey!
Allah is with us!
Are you guys okay, huh?
My Bey!
I knew nothing would happen to you!
I knew it!
Ah! My Konur!
Bamsı Bey!
I hope you are okay.
Thanks to you, Bamsı Bey.
Thanks to you.
My Osman!
Abdurrahman Ghazi!
My Osman.
Abdurrahman Ghazi...
...how's the situation at the Tent?
We found out Dündar Bey was the one who
betrayed us.
It seems like my uncle has sold his soul
to Mongol dogs!
He thinks the only way to save my life
is cooperating with Geyhatu.
So it seems the news that went to Konya...
...didn't go there to save your life.
He tried drive a wedge between Balgay and
Geyhatu...
...as he sees it.
We can't accomplish anything with
laziness, questions, and lies!
It's certain who our enemies are!
My uncle has been drinking from the
Byzantine fountains lately.
If one can't fight like an Alp...
...one must know when to step aside.
You look thoughtful, Bamsı Bey.
I hope it's for good.
My Osman.
I heard Samsa met one of the Mongol
commanders.
I can't stop thinking of this.
So it seems Balgay will try to negotiate
with Samsa Bey.
Samsa Bey has evacuated his Tent, my Bey.
It seems he went to mountains with his
Alps.
Selamün aleyküm.
Aleyküm selam.
Sofia...
...knows Samsa Bey is present at
Şahin Hill, my Bey.
Sofia will try to provoke Balgay.
Samsa Bey is in danger.
We need to save him as soon as possible.
We will ambush them in such a way...
...that we will hit two birds with one
stone.
Both Balgay and Sofia.
My Bey.
Sofia is smart.
Do you think she will get tricked?
She must be alert by now.
Sıddık...
Will become Salvador and tell her where
Sheikh Edebali is.
She can't resist this bait.
My Bey.
Did you evacuate women and children?
Alps are taking care of that, my Bey.
It won't take much time.
Why are you not guiding them?
My Bey.
I want to fight and become a martyr if
you'll allow me..
The Hill of Martyrs is full, my Valiant.
And there won't be space anytime soon.
I need you alive...
...so that we can fight against
persecutions side by side.
So many people will get warm with the fire
of freedom we will light.
And many savages will burn.
We will save ummah before they lose their
hope...
...with Turkish justice even it means we
die while fighting.
But while we are alive we won't give
any of our soil to heathens.
Our enemies has gathered together to fight
against all Turks.
But there is one thing they forgot.
If they have evil on their side.
Turks will not stop fighting!
Allahu Akbar!
Zöhre Hatun!
Come here.
Sit down.
Let's talk for a while.
I'm doing nothing but keeping myself busy
with this.
After all my heart beats like a bird.
Trouble after trouble.
What have you been up to?
Where did you come from?
My Aygül doesn't feel well.
I went to find some mint but I couldn't
find any.
So I only picked these up.
I already had some linden at my Tent.
So I came back to boil some.
May Allah give health to your daughter.
Thank you.
What do you think about the Tent, Zöhre?
Perhaps you understand more than me.
You must know what is on Dündar Bey's
mind.
Only Allah knows about our end, Selcan
Hatun.
We can't know what Dündar Bey is thinking.
Can't you see he is fighting with both
Mongols and Osman.
So...
...you don't know yet.
Do you know what happened?
They found the fardel you sent Batur in
the forest.
In the forest?
You gave it to me.
And I gave it to Bala after I told her
it's from you.
So?
So...
...there were blood everywhere.
And the fardel stands at some corner.
Did she die?
May Allah forbid that.
Bala Hatun is lost.
May Allah allow us to find her as soon as
possible.
We may tell Dündar Bey.
Maybe he can do something about this..
No.
Thank you.
We must not tell Dündar Bey at all.
They are looking for her everywhere.
Ahis will find her if Allah helps them.
May Allah be with them, Selcan Hatun.
May Allah be with them.
Good.
Let us know if you get any news.
May our Mother Mary protect you, Sofia.
May she give you extra strength to destroy
our enemies for our cause.
Today we will reach our destiny for which
we waited for too long.
In the name of Master Yannis!
This will cut down all the obstacles you
will come across.
In the name of Master Yannis!
Master Yannis, I will bring Osman who
has recently fallen from grace.
He will pay the price of what he did to
us.
You are the leaders of my army.
First, Princess Sofia.
Then, Andreas.
And, you Helen.
And of course...
...Salvador.
Today is also your day of Destiny.
You'll get you share from our victory.
Or from our crushing strength.
I'm ready to give my life for our cause,
Master.
My children.
Rise!
Go and arm your swords!
Destroy all the obstacles on our path!
Capture Osman dead or alive!
And bring him to me!
Go now!
Godspeed!
In the name of Master Yannis!
Samsa!
You death has arrived!
It's shahada!
Shahada!
And it's our duty!
Allahu Akbar!
My Bey!
Çetin Han!
Çetin!
Talk to me!
Resist, my brother!
Samsa.
We are here, Samsa Bey!
Samsa Bey!
All the persecutions you have committed...
...did you think you could get away from
them?
Tens of our Martyr's blood are on your
hands!
Did you think we would forgive...
...and forget?
I will drown you in your own blood.
Stop!
What did you bring me, Sofia?
Who are those people who want to spoil me?
Minor rulers around our city...
...sent these gifts to reveal their
loyalty to you.
I will host those rulers and you in my
castle tonight.
Did they send all these gold because they
are afraid to come to my Tent ?
Maybe, maybe not.
Just like we wanted.
They sought asylum under my roof because
they fear you.
We pull their strings from now on.
All of them are scared.
And hopeless.
What else can they do...
...except obeying mighty Balgay.
Two of my best scouts...
...will guide you through Şahin Hill...
...to find Samsa Bey.
Is that so?
You come here!
Who's that imbecile?
Osman's most-trusted man.
So that you're the one who entered
into Osman's command and...
made him believe that you're a Muslim.
Yes, mighty Balgay.
Do you know where Osman is?
No, mighty Balgay.
But I know where Edebalı is.
While your commanders get through
with Samsa in Şahin Hill...
I'll take Edebalı.
My warrior queen Sofia.
I'll bring Edebalı's and his
daughter's heads to you...
in the presence of landlords' tonight.
I hope your nökers (soldiers) bring
Osman's Alps' heads.
Today is the day of blood, Sofia.
Dark spirits are so hungry that...
it won't be easy at all to feed them...
without finding Osman.
Take his tongue!
I'll lance his mind before his body.
Let's see what he knows.
You don't know who you go against.
You'll know! You will!
I'll show you.
Alps! Take care of the wounded.
Thanks, Osman Bey.
You saved us.
While the unbelievers trouble us...
it's not good for us to separate.
I called you naive...
but it's obvious that I'm wrong.
I feel bad. Give me your blessings.
I give you my blessings.
All the Kayı tent talks
about your bravery.
Your bravery gave hope to
the innocents, Samsa Bey.
I did what's right.
The enemy is strong, the road is long.
But I see that friends are tough.
Thank you for your heart and weapon.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Mashaallah! (Praise be)
My valiants.
From now on, valiants are...
together.
Unbelievers should be afraid now.
My Gündüz! Where are you going?
I sent Alps yesterday night. I still
haven't heard from them.
I can't stay anymore.
- I should help my brother.
- My Gündüz!
Osman has saved himself.
He'll let you know.
Hatun! I can't stay here
while my brother...
fights with Mongols!
I should help Osman.
Ayşe. You won't go to that tent.
You won't go anyone's tent who call
my uncle their Bey.
My Gündüz. Please...
Take care of yourself.
You too, Hatun.
Talk!
I'll kill all of you.
You'll understand the power of Mongols!
Tell us what you know!
Abbar. Stop.
He killed so many innocents,
Konur brother.
- We should do more to that dog.
- He is a captive.
Whatever it is, we shouldn't
act like that.
Leave please.
I'll make him talk.
Who called you Kongar?
- Who gave you this name?
- My name...
... was given by a holy one.
So I could be known in battles.
- What is this on your neck?
- How should I know?
Now tell me.
- Why do I have the same one? Tell me!
- Are you interrogating me?
Göktuğ! My brother!
You're my brother!
I am your brother!
I'm Konur.
Your brother Konur.
Do you think I'm a child?
Do you think you can fool
Kongar like this?
How could you forget our father
who the Mongols killed?
I'm a Mongol. Mongol! My parents died
in a battle!
Göktuğ! They took your soul!
They took your mind.
How could you forget this sign...
... and our burned down Tent. How?
- Father?
- Konur. Göktuğ.
Father!
I'm a Mongol. Mongol!
Let's assume you forgot this birthmark,
our grandfather İlptekin Alp...
... and our mother who was killed.
Did you forget yourself?
Did you forget our lord we prayed...
Did you forget our Prophet we said
we would die for? Tell me, Göktuğ!
Did you forget them?
Brother!
- Brother!
Konur Brother.
Bring that dog here.
Listen to me carefully.
While I'm here, no one can hurt you.
They can't touch you without fighting me!
Do you understand? No one can touch you.
Don't you worry.
Don't worry. Don't!
Go, you Mongol dog! Move!
Go!
Where are you going, Gündüz?
Do you have something to say to Geyhatu?
What are you talking about?
Balgay knows everything.
You'll come with me.
What if I don't?
I didn't ask you if you want
to come with me.
You will come with me, I said.
What did I say?
If a Mongol gives you an order...
... you abide by it.
- You did a good job, Salvador.
- Osman and his Alps will be here soon.
Surround the place.
No one will get out of here alive.
Why?
Why did you tell Geyhatu, Gündüz?
Who told this to you?
Since you made Balgay your enemy...
... you have decided your fate.
I don't know who is confusing you, but...
Do you know how those...
... who torture the Kayıs die?
You will eventually.
You were vicious at the moorland.
And you're the same in Söğüt.
You changed a little bit.
- But your behaviors are the same.
- Your hands are full of blood now, Cerkutay.
Osman will kill you if I can't.
You'll die all.
- Salamun Alaikum.
- Alaikum Salaam.
- Salamun Alaikum, my Sheikh.
I brought you the regards of Osman Bey.
Salvador!
You traitor!
Kill them all!
It's hard to be a Turk, Sofia.
You go against the cruel ones
because of innocent ones.
But it's harder not to be a Turk.
Because you go against the Turks.
We'll kill you all.
- Princess!
- Shut up!
Tell everyone that...
It doesn't matter if the seven
worlds come at us.
Osman's war has started!
Allahu Akbar! Allahu Akbar!
Allahu Akbar! (Allah is the greatest!)